Pietro Belluschi Papers
Pietro Belluschi Papers
- Architectural projects, numbered
  - 701 Peter Kerr Beach Cottage, Gearhart, OR [Residential], 1941
    - Drawings (Tube 552)
    - Photographs (Box 435)
    - Photographs, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 2)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 250)
  - 702 Wheerie Tailoring Co., Pittock Block, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1941
    - Correspondence (Box 135)
    - Drawings (Tube 393)
    - Photographs, name spelled "Wherrie" (Box 436)
    - Shop drawings, name spelled "Wherrie" (Box 379)
  - 703 Coats Residence, Netants Bay [Residential], 1941
    - Correspondence (Box 135)
    - Drawings (Tube 393)
    - Photographs, includes Christmas photo card (Box 436)
    - Photographs (Oversize 4)
    - Shop drawings (Box 379)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 250)
  - 704 Pacific Tel & Tel Co. Pendleton, Pendleton, OR [Commercial], 1942
    - Correspondence (Box 135)
    - Drawings (Tube 394)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 250)
  - 705 Boiler-Makers Union Building, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1942
    - Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 135)
    - Drawings (Tube 394)
    - Photographs (Box 436)
    - Shop drawings (Box 379)
    - Shop drawings (Box 379)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 251)
  - 706 Reconsignment Depot, Pasco, WA [Other]
    - Correspondence (Box 135)
    - Shop drawings (Box 380)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 251)
  - 707 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 135)
  - 709 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 135)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 251)
  - 710 [unknown]
    - Correspondence, 4 folders (Box 136)
  - 711 [unknown]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 136)
  - 712 Pocatello Air Base, Idaho Falls, ID [Government]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 136)
    - Drawings (Tube 394)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 251)
  - 713 Walla Walla Hospital, Walla Walla, WA [Hospital], 1942
    - Correspondence (Box 137)
    - Drawings (Tube 394)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 251)
  - 714 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 137)
  - 715 Dinwiddie Couples Housing DFH, Portland, OR [Residential], 1942
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 137)
    - Drawings (Tube 395)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 251)
  - 716 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 137)
  - 717 Demountable Barracks [Residential], 1942
    - Correspondence (Box 137)
    - Drawings (Tube 395)
  - 718 Oregon Mutual Life Insurance Co. [Commercial]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 137)
    - Shop drawings (Box 380)
  - 719 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 137)
  - 721 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 137)
  - 722 [unknown]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 138)
  - 723 Wright Residence, Portland, OR [Residential], 1942
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 8)
    - Drawings (Tube 395)
  - 724 Horizontal Construction [Commercial]
    - Drawings
  - 725 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
  - 727 Ross C. Hammond Office, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1943
    - Drawings (Tube 395)
  - 728 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
  - 729 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
  - 730 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
  - 731 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
  - 732 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
  - 733 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
  - 734 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
  - 735 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
  - 736 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
  - 737 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
  - 738 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
  - 739 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
  - 740 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
  - 741 Red Cross [Institutional], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 138)
    - Drawings (Tube 396)
  - 743 [unknown]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 139)
  - 744 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 251)
  - 745 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
  - 746 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
  - 747 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
  - 754 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
  - 755 Andruss Monument and Marker; Houses for Defense Workers [Monument]
    - Drawings (Tube 396)
  - 756 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
  - 757 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
  - 758 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
  - 761 Office Building for Architectural Forum, NYC, NY [Commercial], 1943
    - Drawings (Tube 396)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 9 / 4; 9 / 5)
  - 762 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
  - 763 Barry Brownell Residence [Residential], 1943
    - Drawings (Tube 400)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 9 / 3)
  - 764 Port Orchard High School [Educational]
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
    - Photographs (Box 436)
  - 765 United War Chest Alterations [Institutional], 1943
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
    - Drawings (Tube 396)
    - Photographs, job title given as "Civic Campaign Center" (Box 436)
  - 766 University Homes [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
    - Photographs (Box 436)
  - 767 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
  - 768 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
  - 769 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
  - 770 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 139)
  - 771 [unknown]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 140)
  - 772 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 140)
  - 773 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 140)
  - 774 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 140)
  - 775 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 140)
  - 776 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 140)
  - 778 Riverview Cemetery Chapel Additions, Portland, OR [Religious], 1944
    - Correspondence, job 778.1 (Box 140)
    - Correspondence, job 778.2 (Box 140)
    - Drawings (Tube 485)
    - Photographs, includes floor plan; 2 folders (Box 436)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 380)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 251)
    - [unidentified item], 5 items ("flat storage")
  - 781 St. Thomas More [Catholic Church] Grade School and Rectory [Religious]
    - Correspondence (Box 141)
    - Drawings
    - Shop drawings (Box 380)
    - Specifications (Box 442)
  - 782 Willamette University, Men's Dorm, Salem, OR [Educational], 1946
    - Correspondence (Box 141)
    - Correspondence, job 782.1; 3 folders (Box 141)
    - Correspondence, job 782.2 (Box 141)
    - Correspondence, job 782.4 (Box 141)
    - Correspondence, job 782.5 (Box 142)
    - Correspondence, job 782.6 (Box 142)
    - Drawings (Tube 397)
    - Drawings (Tube 398)
    - Photographs, includes college promotional pamphlet (Box 436)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 380)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 251)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 783 [unknown]
    - Correspondence, 5 folders (Box 142)
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 143)
  - 784 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 143)
  - 785 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 143)
  - 786 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 143)
  - 787 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 143)
  - 788 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 143)
  - 790 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 143)
  - 792 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 143)
  - 793 [unknown]
    - Correspondence, job 793-A (Box 143)
    - Correspondence, job 793-B (Box 143)
    - Correspondence, job 793-B (Box 144)
    - Correspondence, job 793-C; 3 folders (Box 144)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 794 First Methodist Church, Portland, OR [Religious], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 144)
    - Drawings (Tube 558)
    - Photographs, job title given as "Junior Methodist Church Chapel" (Box 436)
    - [unidentified item], 2 items ("flat storage")
  - 796 J. L. Flynn Residence, Oswego, OR [Residential], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 144)
    - Drawings (Tube 526)
  - 797 Bagby Downs
    - Correspondence (Box 144)
    - Photographs, includes negatives; 2 folders (Box 436)
    - Photographs (Oversize 4)
  - 799 Washington Project
    - Photographs (Box 436)
  - 800 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 144)
  - 802 Everatte Residence [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 144)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:5)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 803 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 144)
  - 804 Adams Memorial [Monument]
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:5)
  - 805 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
  - 806 Radio KGW & KEX Stations, Portland, OR [Other]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 145)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:5)
  - 808 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
  - 809 Vincent Residence, Palm Springs, CA [Residential], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:5)
    - Drawings (Tube 536)
    - Photographs (Box 436)
    - Shop drawings (Box 381)
  - 811 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
  - 812 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
  - 813 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
  - 815 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
    - Specifications (Box 442)
  - 818 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
  - 819 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
  - 821 Northwestern Laundry Co. [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:5)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 822 D. C. Burkes House [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
    - Drawings (Tube 401)
    - Shop drawings (Box 381)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 823 F. Smith Residence, Portland, OR [Residential]
    - Drawings (Tube 400)
  - 824 Waddles Drive-in Restaurant [Other]
    - Shop drawings (Box 381)
  - 825 Beauty Shop for PPG [Pittsburgh Plate Glass] [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
    - Drawings (Tube 400)
  - 827 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
  - 828 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
  - 830 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
    - Specifications (Box 442)
  - 831 Title and Trust Building, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
    - Drawings (Tube 400)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 832 McLean Apartments [Residential]
    - Drawings (Tube 400)
  - 834 Pollard Residence, Portland, OR [Residential], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
    - Drawings (Tube 400)
  - 835 St. Andrew's Hotel Kitchen, Portland, OR [Residential], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 145)
    - Drawings (Tube 400)
    - Shop drawings (Box 381)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 836 Linfield College [Educational]
    - Correspondence (Box 146)
    - Photographs, includes floor plan, aerial drawings (Box 436)
    - Photographs (Oversize 4)
  - 837 Arlington Club [Institutional]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 146)
    - Shop drawings (Box 381)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 838 Multnomah Hotel Air Conditioning, Portland, OR [Residential], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 146)
    - Drawings (Tube 402)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 839 Kortin Music Co., Longview, WA [Commercial], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 146)
    - Drawings (Tube 399)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 4 items (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
    - Shop drawings, named spelled "Korton"; 2 folders (Box 382)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 840 Gallucci [Belluschi?] House, Portland, OR [Residential], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 146)
    - Drawings (Tube 399)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 841 L. A. Courtemanche Farm Implements Service Building, McMinnville, OR [Other], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 146)
    - Drawings (Tube 399)
    - Shop drawings (Box 382)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 842 Farmhouse Alterations [Residential]
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:4)
    - Photographs (Box 436)
  - 843 Sigart Branch, U.S. Bank [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 146)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:4)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 844 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 146)
  - 845 Northwest Airlines Alterations [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 146)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:4)
    - Photographs, 2 folders; includes negatives, blueprints, magazine clippings (Box 436)
    - Shop drawings (Box 382)
  - 846 DeCico Building [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 147)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:4)
  - 847 Prentiss Residence [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 147)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:2)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:2)
    - Shop drawings (Box 382)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 848 W. R. Caswell House [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 147)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:2)
  - 849 Station KALE Radio Room [Other]
    - Correspondence (Box 147)
    - Drawings (Tube 362:C:2)
  - 850 Schramm House, Salem, OR [Residential], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 147)
    - Drawings (Tube 404)
  - 851 Phil. Transfer Co., Portland, OR [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 147)
    - Drawings (Tube 403)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 852 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 147)
  - 853 U.S. Bank, Milwaukie-Powell Branch [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 147)
    - Drawings (Tube 403)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 854 Linfield College, Infirmary, McMinnville, OR [Educational], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 147)
    - Drawings (Tube 403)
    - Shop drawings (Box 382)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 855 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 147)
  - 856 [unknown]
    - Correspondence (Box 147)
  - 858 C. H. Palmer House [Residential], 1944
    - Drawings (Tube 403)
  - 859 Charles Sprague Lodge, Little North Santiam River, OR [Residential], 1947
    - Correspondence (Box 147)
    - Drawings (Tube 548)
    - Photographs (Box 436)
    - Photographs (Oversize 4)
  - 861 Oregonian Building [Commercial]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 147)
    - Correspondence, job 861-B (Box 147)
    - Correspondence, job 861-C (Box 147)
    - Correspondence, job 861-D (Box 148)
    - Correspondence, job 861-E; 2 folders (Box 148)
    - Correspondence, job 861-F; 2 folders (Box 148)
    - Correspondence, job 861-G (Box 148)
    - Correspondence, job 861-G (Box 149)
    - Correspondence, job 861-H; 2 folders (Box 149)
    - Correspondence, job 861-I; 2 folders (Box 149)
    - Correspondence, job 861-J (Box 149)
    - Correspondence, job 861-J (Box 150)
    - Correspondence, job 861-K; 2 folders (Box 150)
    - Correspondence, job 861-L; 2 folders (Box 150)
    - Photographs, includes typed captions, photo floor plans, magazine clippings (Box 436)
    - Photographs, 2 folders (Box 437)
    - Photographs (Oversize 4)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 3 items (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
    - Shop drawings (Box 382)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 383)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 384)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 385)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 386)
    - Shop drawings, 4 folders (Box 387)
    - Specifications (Box 443)
  - 862 Montgomery House, Cooper Mtn. [Residential], 1944
    - Drawings (Tube 404)
  - 866 Holy Family Parish, Portland, OR [Religious], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 150)
    - Correspondence (Box 151)
    - Drawings (Tube 405)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 10 items (Drawer 9 / 1; 9 / 2)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 252)
  - 868 KALE Transmitting Station on Mount Scott, Mt. Scott, OR [Other], 1947
    - Correspondence (Box 151)
    - Drawings (Tube 404)
    - Shop drawings (Box 388)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 253)
  - 869 Columbia Brick Works, Portland, OR [Industrial], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 151)
    - Drawings (Tube 404)
  - 870 Esther Foster Shops, for Paul Wallace, Salem, OR [Commercial], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 151)
    - Drawings (Tube 404)
    - Photographs (Box 437)
    - Shop drawings (Box 388)
  - 871 Zimmerman's 12 Mile Store, Gresham, OR [Commercial], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 151)
    - Drawings (Tube 404)
    - Photographs (Box 437)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 253)
  - 872 Beall Pipe and Tank Corp., Portland, OR [Commercial], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 151)
    - Drawings (Tube 407)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 253)
  - 873 Automobile Equip Co., Portland, OR [Commercial], 1945
    - Correspondence, job title given as L. A. Courtemanche, 311 N.E. Oregon (Box 151)
    - Drawings (Tube 407)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 253)
  - 874 Waddles Drive-In Restaurant, Portland, OR [Other], 1945
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 151)
    - Drawings (Tube 406)
    - Photographs (Box 437)
    - Photographs, 2 items (Drawer 8 / 1)
    - Shop drawings (Box 388)
  - 875 Seattle First National Bank, Seattle, WA [Commercial], 1966
    - Drawings (Tube 763)
  - 876 Portland Gas and Coke Co. Hospitality House & Office, Albany, OR [Hospital], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 151)
    - Drawings (Tube 407)
    - Photographs, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 1)
  - 877 Gabriel Fabrication and Erection Co., Portland, OR [Commercial], 1944
    - Drawings (Tube 463)
  - 878 Drake Development, Portland, OR, 1944
    - Drawings (Tube 406)
  - 879 Radio Studio for KGW, Broadway and Jefferson [Other]
    - Correspondence (Box 152)
  - 880 Oregon Physicians Service, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 152)
    - Drawings (Tube 406)
  - 882 United Gas Co., Camas, WA [Commercial], 1944
    - Correspondence (Box 152)
    - Drawings (Tube 406)
  - 883 Oregon Mutual Life Insurance Co. Alts [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 152)
    - Photographs (Box 437)
    - Photographs (Oversize 4)
  - 884 Chamber of Commerce Additions to mezzanine [Government]
    - Correspondence (Box 152)
  - 885 Ungar Building, proposed beauty parlor, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1946
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 152)
    - Drawings (Tube 407)
    - Shop drawings (Box 388)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 253)
  - 888 Reed College Science Building [Educational]
    - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 152)
    - Correspondence, progress reports (Box 153)
    - Photographs (Oversize 4)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 388)
    - Shop drawings (Box 389)
    - Specifications (Box 443)
  - 889 [unknown]
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 253)
  - 890 Equitable Savings and Loan Association, Portland, OR [Commercial]
    - Correspondence, laboratory reports (Box 153)
    - Correspondence, building plans (Box 153)
    - Correspondence, rental plans; 2 folders (Box 153)
    - Correspondence (Box 153)
    - Correspondence, 5 folders (Box 154)
    - Correspondence, 4 folders (Box 155)
    - Correspondence, tenants, tenant costs; 2 folders (Box 155)
    - Correspondence, photographs (Box 191)
    - Drawings, 1946-1949; blueprints of miscellaneous details (Tube 824)
    - Drawings, 1946; blueprints part 1, 1-44 (Tube 848)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 389)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 390)
    - Shop drawings, 3 folders (Box 391)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 253)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 254)
    - Specifications (Box 444)
  - 891 R. Menefee / Menifee Ranchhouse, Yamhill, OR [Residential], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 156)
    - Drawings (Tube 411)
    - Photographs, includes magazine clippings, aerial ground plan (Box 437)
    - Photographs (Oversize 4)
    - Photographs (Oversize 5)
    - Photographs, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 2)
    - Shop drawings, name given as "P. L. Menefee" (Box 391)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 254)
  - 892 Buck Ranch House [Residential]
    - Miscellaneous, miscellaneous notes, no drawings (Tube 407)
  - 893 Packard and Malloy Office building, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 156)
    - Drawings (Tube 407)
  - 894 Catlin School, Portland, OR [Educational], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 156)
    - Drawings (Tube 408)
    - Photographs, gymnasium (Box 437)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 3 items (Drawer 9 / 3)
    - Shop drawings (Box 392)
  - 895 9th St. Grocery and Mrk [Market?] Dalles, The Dalles, OR [Commercial], 1945
    - Correspondence, job title given as "Sawyer Store, The Dalles" (Box 156)
    - Drawings (Tube 411)
    - Photographs (Box 437)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, job title given as "Sawyer's Market"; 1 item (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 254)
  - 896 Sweeney Straub and Dimm Printing Plant, Portland, OR [Industrial], 1946
    - Correspondence (Box 156)
    - Drawings (Tube 408)
  - 897 Berni Brothers Merchandise Mart, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 156)
    - Drawings (Tube 408)
    - Photographs, job title given a "Portland Merchandise"; 1 item (Drawer 8 / 1)
  - 898 Public Service Building [Other]
    - Correspondence (Box 156)
    - Shop drawings (Box 392)
  - 899 Dr Hill Apm'ts. and Office, Salem, OR [Residential], 1946
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
    - Drawings (Tube 408)
  - 900 Buck Ambulance, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
    - Drawings (Tube 411)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 2 items (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 254)
  - 901 Northern School Supply, Portland, OR [Educational], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
    - Drawings (Tube 409)
    - Photographs (Box 437)
    - Shop drawings, 2 folders (Box 392)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 254)
  - 902 Benson Hotel Alterations [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
  - 903 Bates Garage (alternate title: Bates Motoramp), Portland, OR [Residential], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
    - Drawings (Tube 409)
  - 904 Hood River Courthouse, Hood River, OR [Government], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
    - Drawings (Tube 409)
  - 905 Lerner Shops, Property Alterations, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1946
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
    - Drawings (Tube 409)
    - Photographs, 4 items (Drawer 8 / 1)
  - 906 Berni House, Portland, OR [Residential], 1945
    - Drawings (Tube 409)
  - 907 Stork Service Inc., Portland, OR [Commercial], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
    - Drawings (Tube 409)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 254)
  - 908 Sunset Electric Co., Portland, OR [Commercial], 1946
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
    - Drawings, garage (Drawer MCD 4)
    - Drawings (Tube 410)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
  - 909 Edison Building Alterations [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
  - 909-2 [?] Temple B'Nai Jeshuren, Short Hills, NJ [Religious], 1967
    - Drawing (Tube 768)
    - Drawing, preliminary (Tube 769)
    - Drawings, new temple (Tube 908)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 471)
  - 910 Vance Building, Seattle, WA [Commercial], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
    - Drawings (Tube 410)
    - Photographs, 6 items (Drawer 8 / 2)
  - 911 Methodist Church [Religious]
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
  - 912 Luke Roberts House, Portland, OR [Residential], 1945
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
    - Drawings (Tube 410)
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 254)
  - 913 Swettin Building, Portland, OR [Other], 1945
    - Drawings (Tube 410)
  - 914 Sherman Clay Co. [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
    - Drawings
    - Specifications, A. E. Doyle pamphlets (Box 255)
  - 915 Art Museum [Museum]
    - Correspondence (Box 157)
    - Drawings
    - Shop drawings (Oversize 2)
  - 916 Pacific Building for Standard Oil [Commercial]
    - Correspondence, job title given as "Dolph Block" (Box 157)
    - Drawings
  - 917 Standard Oil Co. [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 157)